// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: "1.1",
    question: "Why did the computer sneeze?",
    answer: "Because it got a virus",
    options: [
      "404 error",
      "Because it got a virus",
      "Unknown",
      "Blue screen of death"
    ],
    note: "Source: Made up question."
  },
    {
    numb: "1.2",
    question: "How are elephants and computers similar?",
    answer: "They both have large memories",
    options: [
      "They both have large memories",
      "huh?",
      "I don't get it",
      "This is not a great joke"
    ],
    note: "Source: Made up question."
  },
    {
    numb: "1.3",
    question: "Why did the cat sit on the computer?",
    answer: "To keep an eye on the mouse",
    options: [
      "Porcupine",
      "Zebra",
      "Tiger",
      "To keep an eye on the mouse"
    ],
    note: "Source: Made up question."
  },
    {
    numb: "1.4",
    question: "What's an alien's favorite key?",
    answer: "The space bar",
    options: [
      "The space bar",
      "The esc key",
      "The exclamation mark",
      "The &"
    ],
    note: "Source: Made up question."
  },
    {
    numb: "1.5",
    question: "How do trees use computers?",
    answer: "They log in",
    options: [
      "Fir tree",
      "They log in",
      "Pine tree",
      "Spruce tree"
    ],
    note: "Source: Made up question."
  },
  {
  numb: "1.6",
  question: "What does a website and Cookie Monster have in common?",
  answer: "they both love cookies",
  options: [
    "Elmo is their friend",
    "PBS",
    "something about Sesame Street?",
    "they both love cookies"
  ],
  note: "Source: Made up question."
},
{
    numb: "1.7",
    question: "What do you call a computer that sings?",
    answer: "A-dell",
    options: [
      "Beyonce",
      "Cher",
      "A-dell",
      "Aretha Franklin"
    ],
    note: "Source: Made up question."
},
{
    numb: "1.8",
    question: "Why did the PPT presentation cross the road?",
    answer: "to get to the other slide",
    options: [
      "to get to the other slide",
      "it was jaywalking",
      "can you see my slides?",
      "you're muted"
    ],
    note: "Source: Made up question."
},
{
    numb: "1.9",
    question: "What does a computer eat?",
    answer: "Micro chips, one byte at a time",
    options: [
      "students",
      "my homework",
      "my unsaved files",
      "Micro chips, one byte at a time"
    ],
    note: "Source: Made up question."
},
{
    numb: "1.10",
    question: "What do you call a computer superhero?",
    answer: "A screen saver",
    options: [
      "A screen saver",
      "Batman",
      "Superman",
      "Captain America"
    ],
    note: "Source: Made up question."
},
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ],
  //  note: "Source: Made up question."
  // },
];
